Today we are going to look at three stocks. The first
stock is I Lord. You
can buy it till 1388, 1381, 1395
[Music].
In this our stop loss will be 12601 and 1255
which is the support in monthly and weekly
and our target in this is
1410,
1430,
1450, 1450 is the resistance in monthly and weekly.
If there is a break then
1492,
15 A target can be seen.
The market is negative right now.
Work in limited quantity. If you observe the
monthly and weekly chart, then
its closing for the last four
months is above our stop loss
and the chart is also positive.
If you look at the monthly chart, we have
got a good closing.
Next talk is SBI Life.
You can buy it till 1357, 1364, 1370.
Our stop loss in this will be 1300 and the
target is
1380 which is the monthly and weekly.  There
is resistance in it, if there is a break, then
1400 1450 target can be seen,
new 52 wak can be seen in the stock, the
closing is above 52 wak,
so this is a good sign,
so you can make a trade in limited quantities in this also, the
next stock is
our Chat Company Limited,
it is a jute product company, the
stock was listed in June 2022,
if you look at the weekly chart, then the
closing is good in the weekly chart,
in this our stop loss will be
1140 and the target is
1353 and 1353, if there is a break, then
targets up to 1380 1400 can be seen, the
monthly and weekly candle is
above the resistance, closing is above the resistance in the weekly,
so you can study these charts also,
you must study the charts of all three stocks, do
not
take direct entry in any stock at all, in the last time we had three stocks
Chambal
Fertilizer
stock has returned from 30, market is also
negative, first target was good,
next stock MC did
well, MC also reversed after first hit
and the third stock was probably Hindustan
Unilever, this stock went up a bit and reversed
but stop loss has not been hit yet,
this stock continues to be range bound, please see the reverse.